let quiz = [
    {
        question: "In which of the following years, the UNO constituted?",
        option: [
            "A) 1920",
            "B) 1945",
            "C) 1965",
            "D) 1995",
            ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which among the following is the largest artificial lake in the world?",
        option: [
            "A) Lake Volta",
            "B) Rihand Dam",
            "C) Lake Victoria",
            "D) Lake Kariba",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which among the following is related to Temple of Diana?",
        option: [
            " A) Iraq",
            " B) Egypt",
            " C) Rome",
            " D) Greek",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            " In reference to Lawn Tennis, what is the height of the net?",
        option: [
            "A) 4 feet",
            "B) 3 feet ",
            "C) 3.7 feet",
            "D) 5.5 feet",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            " Which among the following is related to Colossus?",
        option: [
            "A) Iraq ",
            "B) Egypt ",
            "C) Roman",
            "D) Greek ",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
        " As per the Census 2011, what is the literacy of India?",
        option:[
            "A) 74 percent",
            "B) 82 percent",
            "C) 65 percent",
            "D) 76 percent",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
        " Pandit Shailesh Bhagwat is related to ?",
        option:[
            "A) Shehnai",
            "B) Violin",
            "C) Veena",
            "D) Santoor",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
        "Where Prince of Wales Museum is located ?",
        option:[
            "A) Karnataka ",
            "B) Odisha ",
            "C) Maharashtra ",
            "D) Tamil Nadu ",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
        " Where St. George Fort is located ?",
        option:[
            "A) Chennai ",
            "B) Jammu & Kashmir ",
            "C) Agra ",
            "D) Lucknow ",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
        "Which among the following is the biggest dam in the world?",
        option:[
            "A) Three Gorges Dam",
            "B) Jinping-I Dam",
            "C) Nurek Dam",
            "D) Robert-Bourassa Dam",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    

    
     
];




